http://www.pennzoil.com/en_us/cookie-policy.html

Cookie Policy
In this policy we use the term “cookies” to refer to cookies and other similar technologies covered by the EU Directive on privacy in electronic communications. What is a cookie? A cookie is a small piece of data that a website asks your browser to store on your computer or mobile device. The cookie allows the website to "remember" your actions or preferences over time. Most Internet browsers support cookies; however, users can set their browsers to decline certain types of cookies or specific cookies. Further, users can delete cookies at any time. Why do we use cookies? We use cookies to learn how you interact with our content and to improve your experience when visiting our website(s). For example, some cookies remember your language or preferences so that you do not have to repeatedly make these choices when you visit one of our websites. We also use cookies to help us with geolocation tracking in order to present you with the closest Pennzoil sites and office locations. Additionally, cookies allow us to serve you specific content, such as videos on our website(s). We may employ the learnings of your behavior on our website(s) to serve you with targeted advertisements on third-party website(s) in an effort to “re-market” our products and services to you. What types of cookies do we use? First-Party and Third-Party Cookies We use both first-party and third-party cookies on our website. First-party cookies are cookies issued from the pennzoil.com domain that are generally used to identify language and location preferences or render basic site functionality. Third-party cookies belong to and are managed by other parties, such as Pennzoil business partners or service providers. These cookies may be required to render certain forms, such as the submission of a job application, or to allow for some advertising outside of the Pennzoil website. Session Cookies Session cookies are temporary cookies that are used to remember you during the course of your visit to the website, and they expire when you close the web browser. Persistent Cookies Persistent cookies are used to remember your preferences within the website and remain on your desktop or mobile device even after you close your browser or restart your computer. We use these cookies to analyse user behavior to establish visit patterns so that we can improve our website functionality for you and others who visit our website(s). These cookies also allow us to serve you with targeted advertising and measure the effectiveness of our site functionality and advertising. How are cookies used for advertising purposes? Cookies and ad technology such as web beacons, pixels, and anonymous ad network tags help us serve relevant ads to you more effectively. They also help us collect aggregated audit data, research, and performance reporting for advertisers. Pixels enable us to understand and improve the delivery of ads to you, and know when certain ads have been shown to you. Since your web browser may request advertisements and web beacons directly from ad network servers, these networks can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. Although we do not use cookies to create a profile of your browsing behavior on third-party sites, we do use aggregate data from third parties to show you relevant, interest-based advertising. We do not provide any personal information that we collect to advertisers. You can opt out of off-site and third-party-informed advertising by adjusting your cookie settings. Opting out will not remove advertising from the pages you visit, but, instead, opting out will result in the ads you see not being matched to your interests. This implies that the ad(s) you see will not be matched to your interests by those specific cookies. How are third party cookies used? For some of the functions within our websites we use third party suppliers, for example, when you visit a page with videos embedded from or links to YouTube. These videos or links (and any other content from third party suppliers) may contain third party cookies, and we encourage you to consult the privacy policies of these third party vendors on their websites for information regarding their use of cookies. How do I reject and delete cookies? You can choose to reject or block all or specific types of cookies set by virtue of your visit to a Pennzoil website by clicking on the cookie preferences on our website(s). You can change your preferences for Pennzoil websites and/or the websites of any third party suppliers by changing your browser settings. Please note that most browsers automatically accept cookies. Therefore, if you do not wish cookies to be used, you may need to actively delete or block the cookies. If you reject the use of cookies, you will still be able to visit our websites but some of the functions may not work correctly. You may also visit www.allaboutcookies.org for details on how to delete or reject cookies and for further information on cookies generally. By using our website without deleting or rejecting some or all cookies, you agree that we can place those cookies that you have not deleted or rejected on your device.
Cookie Description Opt-Out Link/More details regarding specific privacy policy
Adobe Analytics We use Adobe Analytics to understand how users arrive on our website(s) and how they engage with us on the website. The data is used to improve the user experience. No personal data is collected and the data is not shared with any third party. http://www.adobe.com/uk/privacy/opt-out.html
Atlas Atlas tags allow us to measure the performance of our advertising across devices, browsers and publishers. https://atlassolutions.com/privacy-policy/
Crazy Egg
We use the Crazy Egg service to help us improve the visitor experience and performance of our website. Crazy Egg provides graphical, video and text analysis of visitor behaviour on a website. It tracks where visitors click and allows us to fine-tune the layout and design of our web pages.
https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy
Bing The Bing Ads Universal Event Tracking tag helps us understand how our Bing campaigns perform by tracking actions on Shell websites once ads have been clicked. https://choice.microsoft.com/en-US/opt-out
DoubleClick Floodlight DoubleClick Floodlight cookies enable us to understand if you complete certain actions on our website(s) after you have seen or clicked through one of our display/ video advertisements served on Google or other platforms via DoubleClick. DoubleClick uses this cookie to understand the content with which you have engaged on our website(s) so they may subsequently deliver some targeted advertisements to you. https://support.google.com/ds/answer/2839090?hl=en
Facebook Facebook helps you stay in touch with your network through their website/ mobile application. We make it easier for you to share any content of interest on Facebook and sometimes, we may present with some targeted adverts on Facebook based on your engagement with our website(s). https://en-gb.facebook.com/help/568137493302217
Google Adwords Conversion Google Adwords Conversion tracking cookies enable us to understand if you complete certain actions on our website(s) after you have seen or clicked through one of our adverts served via Google. https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en
Google Analytics We use Google Analytics to understand how our media campaigns work and how you interact with our website in order to improve the user experience. https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Google (Remarketing) Google uses this cookie to understand what content you have engaged with on our websites so that they are able to deliver some targeted adverts based on the content you have engaged with on our website(s) in order to serve you targeted ads across other Google partner websites. https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en
LinkedIn The LinkedIn insight tag allows us to perform campaign reporting and unlock valuable insights about website visitors that may come via the campaigns we run on LinkedIn. https://www.linkedin.com/help/lms/answer/65521/the-linkedin-insight-tag-overview?lang=en
Lucid Lucid cookies help us to measure brand lift and brand awareness from our advertising and marketing campaigns. https://luc.id/privacy-policy/
Outbrain Outbrain offers a content marketing service that aims to present users to content that they are interested in, based on their behaviour and preference. The pixel we've added helps with attribution and overall performance. http://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy
Qualtrics Site Intercept Qualtrics Site Intercept helps organizations measure and enhance the experience a web visitor has within their digital media, via optional surveys.  https://www.qualtrics.com/privacy-statement/
Specific Media Specific Media technology is used to deliver targeted messages and video adverts to users based on their engagement on our website(s). http://corp.specificmedia.com/privacy?rid=55c4d1ffb80ea#section_4
The Trade Desk The Trade Desk is an online demand-side platform that provides buying tools for digital media buyers. The conversion pixel we add allows us to track performance and derive insights for media investments made. http://thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy#optout
Tube Mogul Tube Mogul helps us deliver targeted video ads across desktops/ mobile devices and measure their relative performance across the real time inventory available across Tube Mogul partner websites. Tube Mogul is not to collect any Personally Identifiable Information from our website(s).
http://www.tubemogul.com/compliance/privacy-policy/
Turn Turn helps us define audience segments based on your engagement with our website(s) and then, deliver targeted display/video/mobile ads to these anonymous segments. Turn does not collect personal data so they will only know your browser or device but never know your name/contact information. http://www.turn.com/trust/consumer-opt-out
Twitter Twitter provides real time updates from across the globe on the latest trending stories, ideas and opinions from the Twitter accounts or hashtags that you choose to follow. We make it easier for you to share our website content over Twitter. At times, we may present you with some ads on Twitter based on your engagement with our website(s). https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170410
VK This tag collects audience information from the VK Russian Social Network for later remarketing. Audience segmentation will allow for increased efficiency of advertising in VK and a decrease in ad spend for Shell. https://vk.com/ads?act=office_help&terms=1
Xaxis   Xaxis helps us define audience segments based on your engagement with our website(s) and then, deliver targeted display/video/mobile ads to these anonymous segments. Xaxis does not collect personal data so they will only know your browser or device but never know your name/contact information.
https://www.xaxis.com/static/view/privacy-policy
Yahoo The Yahoo! Dot tag assists is in campaign tracking at attribution to help optimize performance. https://developer.yahoo.com/gemini/guide/dottags/managing-dot-tags/
Yandex This tag collects audience information for remarketing within the Yandex Advertising Network. Audience segmentation will allow for increased efficiency of advertising in Yandez and a decrease in ad spend for Shell. https://yandex.com/support/metrica/general/opt-out.xml
YouTube We embed videos or insert links to videos from YouTube on our website(s). As a result, when you visit a page with content embedded from or linked to YouTube, you may be presented with cookies from YouTube. https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en-GB
